<resources>
    <string name="app_name">lab3_p2</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="titleView">titleView</string>
    <string name="descView">descView</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string-array name="recipe_titles">
        <item>Cinnamon Bread</item>
        <item>Million-Dollar Spaghetti</item>
        <item>Simple Macaroni and Cheese</item>
        <item>Stuffed Eggplant Parmesan Rolls</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="recipe_values">
        <item>
            Preheat oven to 350 degrees F (175 degrees C). Grease one 9x5 inch loaf pan.

            Measure flour, 1 cup sugar, baking powder, baking soda, 1 1/2 teaspoons cinnamon, salt, buttermilk, oil, eggs and vanilla into large mixing bowl. Beat 3 minutes. Pour into prepared loaf pan. Smooth top.

            Combine 2 tablespoons white sugar, 1 teaspoon cinnamon and butter, mixing until crumbly. Sprinkle topping over smoothed batter. Using knife, cut in a light swirling motion to give a marbled effect.

            Bake for about 50 minutes. Test with toothpick. When inserted it should come out clean. Remove bread from pan to rack to cool.
        </item>
        <item>
            Preheat oven to 350 degrees F (175 degrees C).

            Bring a large pot of lightly salted water to a boil. Cook spaghetti in the boiling water, stirring occasionally until cooked through but firm to the bite, about 12 minutes. Drain.

            Heat a large skillet over medium-high heat. Cook and stir beef in the hot skillet until browned and crumbly, 5 to 7 minutes; drain and discard grease. Transfer to a bowl and mix spaghetti sauce into ground beef.

            Place half the slices of butter into the bottom of a 9x13-inch casserole dish. Spread half the spaghetti into the dish. Mix cottage cheese, cream cheese, and sour cream together in a bowl; spread mixture over spaghetti. Layer remaining spaghetti over creamy mixture. Top with remaining pats of butter.

            Pour ground beef mixture over spaghetti and spread to cover casserole.

            Bake in the preheated oven for 30 minutes. Spread Cheddar cheese over casserole and continue baking until cheese has melted and is lightly browned, about 15 more minutes.
        </item>


        <item>
            Bring a large pot of lightly salted water to a boil. Cook elbow macaroni in the boiling water, stirring occasionally until cooked through but firm to the bite, 8 minutes. Drain.

            Melt butter in a saucepan over medium heat; stir in flour, salt, and pepper until smooth, about 5 minutes. Slowly pour milk into butter-flour mixture while continuously stirring until mixture is smooth and bubbling, about 5 minutes. Add Cheddar cheese to milk mixture and stir until cheese is melted, 2 to 4 minutes.

            Fold macaroni into cheese sauce until coated.
        </item>


        <item>
            Preheat oven to 400 degrees F (200 degrees C). Grease a 9x13-inch baking dish with butter.

            Slice eggplant into 1/4-inch thick slices lengthwise; discard the end slices with skin.Lay the eggplant slices on paper towels and sprinkle both sides generously with sea salt. Let slices drain for 30 minutes; rinse and pat dry with paper towels.

            Place flour, eggs, and bread crumbs in separate shallow bowls. Dip each eggplant slice in flour and shake off excess; dip into egg and then into bread crumbs.

            Heat vegetable oil in a large skillet over medium heat and fry the slices until golden brown, about 5 minutes per side. Drain on paper towels, place on baking sheets, and refrigerate eggplant for 10 minutes.

            Mix ricotta cheese, Romano cheese, and garlic in a bowl; season to taste with salt and black pepper. Place a cooled eggplant slice onto a work surface and mound 1/3 to 1/2 cup of cheese mixture in the center; roll up slice and place seam side down into the prepared baking sheet. Repeat with remaining slices and cheese filling.

            Bake rolls in the preheated oven until filling is hot, about 25 minutes.
        </item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
